[
  {
    "front": "1",
    "back": "一"
  },
  {
    "front": "2",
    "back": "二"
  },
  {
    "front": "3",
    "back": "三"
  },
  {
    "front": "4",
    "back": "四"
  },
  {
    "front": "5",
    "back": "五"
  },
  {
    "front": "6",
    "back": "六"
  },
  {
    "front": "7",
    "back": "七"
  },
  {
    "front": "8",
    "back": "八"
  },
  {
    "front": "9",
    "back": "九"
  },
  {
    "front": "10",
    "back": "十"
  }
]
